<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <integer-array name="parTime">
        <item>51000</item>  <!-- 1 -->
        <item>45000</item>
        <item>51000</item>
        <item>34000</item>
        <item>36000</item>  <!-- 5 -->
        <item>50000</item>
        <item>18000</item>
        <item>45000</item>
        <item>45000</item>
    </integer-array>

    <string-array name="levelNames">
        <item>The Blue Power-up</item>
        <item>The Pink Power-up</item>
        <item>The Red Power-up</item>
        <item>The Yellow Power-up</item>
        <item>The Green Power-up</item>
        <item>The Multi Power-up</item>



    </string-array>

    <string-array name="infoStrings">
        <item>The blue Power-up will reveal the whole map for 8 seconds. Use this time wisely!</item>
        <item>The pink Power-up will hide all the walls. Do not get lost!</item>
        <item>The red Power-up will invert the controls of the ball. Things are getting harder!</item>
        <item>The yellow Power-up will hide the playingball for 5 seconds.</item>
        <item>The green Power-up will show walls that are inside a certain radius of the ball.</item>
        <item>The multi Power-up will have a randomly chosen effect.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="explenation">
        <item>The hidden maze is a game mode where all the walls are hidden. You can make them appear by hitting them with the ball, but be aware that they will hide again after a couple of seconds. The goal is to collect all the power-ups in the level, but be aware that not all are "helpful" </item>
        <item>The changing maze is a game mode where you have to reach the exit but with a twist. Every few seconds the maze will shift the walls around, so be fast!</item>
        <item>The locked maze is a game mode where you have to reach the exit but not before you have collected the keys to open the doors that are obstructing your path!</item>
        <item>The normal maze is the traditional maze game where you have to reach the exit. Kick back and relax!</item>
    </string-array>



</resources>